"addon"
{
	"addon_game_name"		"NextGen Dota"
	
	"addonname"										"A New Generation"
	
	"yes"											"Yes"
	"no"											"No"
	"close"											"Close"

	"wins"											"wins!"
	"win"											"win!"
	"and"											"and"
	"rematch_question"								"Rematch with new heroes?"
	"round"											"Round"
	"in"											"in"
	"ellipses"										"..."
	"rematch_waiting"								"Waiting for other players to accept rematch..."
	"rematch_declined"								"Other player declined rematch"

	"gameinfo_nav_howto"							"How to Play"
	"gameinfo_nav_about"							"About"






	"gameinfo_main_intro1"							"That's probably something Valve will say when they begin developing new heroes for Dota 2. "
	"gameinfo_main_intro2"							"Having the opportunity to go to TI5 gave me inspiration of how I could be involved with the development of this game. I decided to make a pretty bold claim: I wanted to create the first original DOTA 2 hero in time for TI6. A crazy assertion knowing there hasn't been a new hero since the old days of WC3 Dota, but I wrote it down and kept it in a little book I got from the event. "
	"gameinfo_main_intro3"							"Three months later, I am here now to introduce several hero concepts that I and others have been working on. They aren’t perfect: there are still many bugs and balance issues that need to be looked into. Each one has some unexplored mechanics and themes that make them fun to play, even if they appear to be the current heroes reimagined. I know I’m stepping into Icefrog’s shoes a bit, so I want to put as much time as he does into making these guys. "
	"gameinfo_main_intro4"							"This project is growing. In the next two months, you could be seeing 10 more heroes, all being more involved than the last 10. We will see where this goes, but I have high hopes for what it can become. "
	

	"gameinfo_about_author"							"SwordBacon is the author. Just an average human! "
	"gameinfo_about_specialthanks"					"Special thanks to:"
	"gameinfo_about_thanks1"						"Dirty Joe's Taco Shack (ZizZizZiz) for his concepts and for being a great communicator and friend. "
	"gameinfo_about_thanks2"						"Pongping for his excellent work on Onimusha and other heroes from Playdota. "
	"gameinfo_about_thanks3"						"After Math and ILikeDota for their awesome videos. "
	"gameinfo_about_thanks4"						"Sableye for his lua scripting expertise in developing a hero based on pure physics. "
	"gameinfo_about_thanks5"						"Pizzalol and all other contributors to SpellLibrary, one of the best references I used for this project. "
	"gameinfo_about_thanks6"						"Summer-penguin from Playdota, for helping me bring their ideas to life. "
	"gameinfo_about_thanks7"						"/u/giosgs12 for the custom spell icons for several heroes. "
	"gameinfo_about_thanks8"						"My two Canadian friends for having an extra TI5 ticket to spare. "
	"gameinfo_about_thanks9"						"...and many more to come! "

	"gameinfo_attributions"							""
	"gameinfo_attributions1"						""

	"pick_header_text"								"Choose your hero:"
	"pick_header_waiting_for_opponent"				"Waiting for other players..."


	"pick"											"Pick"
	"random"										"Random"

	"pick_tips_nohero"								"Click a hero to learn more."

	"tips_header"									"Tips for fighting"
	"tips_dont_show_again"							"Don't show me this again"

	"tips_vs_bounty_hunter_1"					"Slows and stuns have a greater effect on Veera than almost any other hero."
	"tips_vs_bounty_hunter_2"					"Keep an eye on Veera early on, and try to shut her down while she's weak and squishy."
	"tips_vs_bounty_hunter_3"					"Veera's Pursuit ability forces her to attack you, so make yourself unattackable."

	"tips_vs_venomancer_1"							"Ooze's passive disarms enemies that try to attack from close range. Keep your distance with ranged attacks or magic nukes."
	"tips_vs_venomancer_2"							"You'll likely find a Viscous Ooze in your jungle. Harass him and he will lose too much health to use Slime Trail effectively."
	"tips_vs_venomancer_3"							"None of Ooze's spells pierce magic immunity."

	"tips_vs_phoenix_1"							"Watch your towers when against Scaw'mar, as he can clear waves and destroy them quickly using both his illusion spells."
	"tips_vs_phoenix_2"							"If Scaw'mar mesmerizes you or an ally, you can damage them to remove the effect before they get caught in the middle of Scryer's Circle."
	"tips_vs_phoenix_3"							"Fade Blink is a powerful mobility tool, but it can prematurely stopped with silences and stuns."

	"tips_vs_enchantress_1"							"Last hit her flowers and spores, especially if you're a ranged hero."
	"tips_vs_enchantress_2"							"Don't stick too close to Cherub, you might be put to sleep."
	"tips_vs_enchantress_3"							"Planting flowers consumes Max HP. She can get herself to very low health if she plants too many at once, so take advantage of that!"

	"tips_vs_juggernaut_1"						"Onimusha is very squishy early on, and is easily caught out at low mana."
	"tips_vs_juggernaut_2"						"Battojutsu does not make Onimusha invulnerable, and will deal self-damage if there are no units within the slash range."
	"tips_vs_juggernaut_3"						"Onimusha has a much higher attack speed and longer range in Orochi form. If you see glowing red particles, he is going to transform!"

	"tips_vs_nyx_assassin_1"						"Do not underestimate the effect of Blight and Wither in the laning phase, or even during teamfights."
	"tips_vs_nyx_assassin_2"						"Though it's hard to see Suna when he is burrowed, he is not invisible, so you can see him coming if you are attentive."
	"tips_vs_nyx_assassin_3"						"Sometimes, taking a few extra seconds to kill an enemy isn't a bad idea, if you know Dead Man's Chest has been used on them."
	
	"tips_vs_skywrath_mage_1"					"Try to bait out his spells, and stun him during Typhoon's long cast time."
	"tips_vs_skywrath_mage_2"					"Expect unexpected ganks from Zulf with his Jet Stream, and keep wards on cliffs!"
	"tips_vs_skywrath_mage_3"					"Zulf's Cyclone Traps can be triggered by any unit, use this to your advantage if certain paths are blocked. "

	"tips_vs_skeleton_king_1"						"Zeros can spend money to grant a powerful effect on a short cooldown. Try purging heroes that are affected so his money goes to waste."
	"tips_vs_skeleton_king_2"						"Don't underestimate Poverty and Blade of Malice, especially if you are harassing Zeros and not last hitting."
	"tips_vs_skeleton_king_3"						"Kill the golden statue fast, and you might get a nice reward. Make sure Zeros doesn't steal it from you, however."
	
	"tips_vs_riki_1"							"Be watchful of the buffs you have to spot any Trap Doors laying about."
    "tips_vs_riki_2"							"Even weak dispels remove Trick Boxes on you."
	"tips_vs_riki_3"							"Never underestimate the Trickster, or anyone on his team."
	
	"tips_vs_disruptor_1"							"Silences shuts this hero down hard."
	"tips_vs_disruptor_2"							"Try to bait out his ultimate to lay down extra damage."
	"tips_vs_disruptor_3"							"Try not to let the fight drag on with Stryder, or he will overwhelm you."
	

	"lorem_ipsum"									"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Proin elit elit, facilisis eu malesuada porttitor, dictum convallis sapien."

}